Guide to the Communications Workers of America, Local 1180 Records WAG.063
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America, Local 1180 Records
1956-1986, 2007-ongoing
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America. Local 1180 (New York, N.Y.)
Cheliotes, Arthur
WAG.063
13.25 Linear Feet in 13 record cartons and 1 folder.
2 websites in 2 archived websites.
Communications Workers of America, Local 1180 had its origins in the Municipal Management Society (founded in 1954), which represented supervisors working for the City of New York. The MMS affiliated with the CWA in 1965, becoming the CWA's first public-employee local. CWA Local 1180 members include employees in welfare centers, the Board of Education, the public hospitals, the Port Authority, and the state and city court systems. The collection contains minutes, correspondence, bargaining files, general files, and grievance and arbitration files.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by President Arthur Cheliotes on behalf of the Communications Workers of America, Local 1180, in 1988. The accession numbers assoicated with this gift are 1988.012 and 1988.014.
http://www.cwa1180.org/ was initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2007 as part of the Labor Unions and Organizations (U.S.) Web Archive. In November 2015, this website was migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2023, https://ftunited.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2023.063.
Historical Note
CWA Local 1180 had its origins in the Municipal Management Society (MMS), a group founded in 1954 to represent Grade 5 Clerks in the New York City civil service who were considered to have managerial responsibilities. The new organization soon had about 120 members, drawn from nearly every agency in city government.
In 1960 New York City agreed to collective bargaining with unions representing specific classes of workers employed in more than one department, and this ushered in a decade of rapid organization of municipal employees by several unions. The MMS, under president James Gaffney, launched a campaign to become the bargaining unit for administrative employees; this required affiliation with an AFL-CIO international union. After discussions with several unions, the MMS membership voted to join the Communications Workers of America, and in May 1965 the MMS was chartered as CWA Local 1180, the first public employees' local in the CWA. The new local proceeded to bargaining on behalf of approximately 2,000 members. After many grueling months of negotiations, its first contract was approved in April 1967.
The following decades saw the rapid growth of public-sector membership in CWA. The city's severe fiscal crisis of the 1970s resulted in some concessions affecting newer members, but Local President Leonard Katz and CWA District 1 Director Morton Bahr managed to protect the membership from massive layoffs. Expansion of the Department of Social Services created new administrative titles, many of them held by women and minorities. A state take-over of the court system in 1977 gave the Local its first experience with bargaining for state workers. The Local's staff grew to include full-time officers, grievance representatives, and managers of the Security Benefits Fund.
After a hard-fought election in 1979, Arthur Cheliotes took over as local president, pledging his opposition to the city's massive program of consolidation of administrative titles (known as "broadbanding") and promising to defend the principle of promotion by competitive exam. Cheliotes, representing a younger generation of leaders within the Local, involved the membership in a wide range of social and legislative issues, including workplace health and safety, participation in electoral campaigns, affordable housing, opposition to Apartheid, and support for labor rights at the national level. The local has an active education program through the Center for Worker Education at City College and the LEAP Program at Queens College. In March 1986 the local initiated a radio program dealing with issues of concern to public employees and other trade unionists. By 1988 the local represented 9,000 members in high-level supervisory titles, including administrator, principal administrative assistant, and computer associate; two thousand members were supervisors in welfare centers. From its beginnings as an association dominated by white males, the local has evolved into a union in which seventy percent of the members are women, many of them African-American, Asian-American or Latino.
Sources:
Augsberger, Deborah. Twenty-five Years: Working for a Better New York, Local 1180, Communications Workers of America. New York: CWA Local 1180, 1991.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains minutes, correspondence, bargaining files, general files, and grievance and arbitration files.
Arrangement
Minutes, Correspondence and Bargaining Files are arranged chronologically. General Files are arranged alphabetically by topic. Most grievances are arranged alphabetically by name.
Organized into seven series:
Series I: Bylaws, Constitution and Minutes
Series II: Correspondence
Series III: Bargaining Files
Series IV: General Files
Series V: Grievances and Arbitration Cases
Series VI: Photographs
Series VII: Archived Websites
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Records of Communications Workers of America, District 1 (WAG 117)
Records of Communications Workers of America, Local 1150 (WAG 59)
Records of the Communications Workers of America (WAG 124)
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Correspondence.; Contracts; Collective bargaining -- State government employees -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- Government employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Clippings (information artifacts); Civil service -- New York (N.Y.); Bylaws (administrative records); New York (N.Y.).; Minutes (administrative records); Labor leaders -- New York (State) -- New York.; Government employee unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Files (document groupings); Employee rights -- New York (State) -- New York; Nonprofit organizations -- Employees -- United States; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Communications Workers of America; Katz, Leonard; Gaffney, James; New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation; Municipal Management Society (New York, N.Y.); Bahr, Morton; Cheliotes, Arthur; New York (N.Y.). Human Resources Administration; New York (N.Y.). Board of Education; New York (N.Y.). Department of Social Services; Communications Workers of America. Local 1180 (New York, N.Y.); Cheliotes, Arthur
- Series I: Bylaws, Constitution and Minutes, 1963-1986
  Scope and Content Note
  Series I: Constitution, Bylaws and Minutes, 1963-1986, contains a constitution and Executive Board minutes dating from the Municipal Management Society period (pre-1965), as well as minutes of the Board, of General Membership Meetings, committee meetings and meetings of the Security Benefits Fund Trustees, 1965-1986.
  - Bylaws, undated, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution (Municipal Management Society), 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board, Jan 1980-Mar 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board, Apr 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board, Jan 1982-Jun 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board, Jul 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Executive Board, Jan 1983-Jun 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Executive Board, Jul 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Executive Board, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Executive Board, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Security Benefits Fund: Trustees, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1974-1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1961-1986
  Series II: Correspondence, 1961-1986, includes exchanges with the CWA international, CWA District 1, Local 1180 members, officers and staff of other unions and organizations, and representatives of management.
  - Communication Workers of America (CWA) International, 1970-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CWA District 1, 1966-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Local President, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Local President, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Local President, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local President, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local President, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local President, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Local President, Jan 1969-Jun 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Local President, Jul 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Local President, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local President, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Local President, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Local President, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Local Vice-President, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board, 1969-1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Members, 1963-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Members, 1974-1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Series III: Bargaining Files, 1965-1985
  Series III: Bargaining Files, 1965-1985, contains reports, drafts of union and management proposals, background reference material, documents reflecting bargaining activity of the Municipal Labor Committee and various New York City and state agencies and departments, with a separate section of files devoted to bargaining within the New York State Judicial Conference and the NYC courts.
  - Bargaining, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining, 1967, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Judicial Conference, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: NYC Unified Court System, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Agreements, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Agreements, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Agreements, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Agreements (Other Public Employee Unions), 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Series IV: General Files, 1956-1986
  Series IV: General Files, 1956-1984, contains correspondence and printed material relating to city and state agencies, including the Judicial Conference, the NYC Human Resources Administration, the NYC Department of Social Services, the Board of Education, the Health and Hospitals Corporation, the Port Authority and others, in which Local 1180 members are or have been employed. There are also files on job classifications, membership applications, benefits, organizing, civil service examinations, the Local's dealings with the NYC Office of Collective Bargaining, and background materials (including contracts) by and about other unions representing city employees.
  - Administrative Assistant, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Assistant: Exams, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Assistant: Exams, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Associate: Exams, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Associate: Exams, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Associate: Exams, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Manager, 1973-1977, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Agency for Child Development, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Agreements (Other Unions), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME, DC 37, 1964, 1970-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME, Local 371, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration Awards: District 1 Locals, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Awards: District 1 Locals, Jan 1977-Aug 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Awards: District 1 Locals, Sep 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Assaults: Income Maintenance Centers, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bahr, Morton, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Barnes, Carmen, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Benefits: Dental Plan, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Benefits: Legal Plan, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Benefits: Legal Plan, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Benefits: Legal Plan, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Benefits: Pensions, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Benefits: Prescriptions, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Board of Education, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Board of Education, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Board of Education, 1973-1977, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Board of Education: Bureau of Supplies, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Board of Estimate, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Boulevard Center: Restructuring, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Broadbanding, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Budgets, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bureau of Child Welfare, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bureau of Child Welfare, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bureau of Medical Assistance, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CETA: Board of Education Organizing, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Citizens' Committee for the Children of New York, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - City of Hope, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Civil Defense: Titles, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1970, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Classification and Compensation, 1967-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Clerical Salaries/Benefits, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Civil Service and Labor, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Community Services Committee, 1978, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Conference: District 1, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University: Training Programs, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - CWA: COPE, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CWA: District 1, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CWA: Local 1181 (merger w/1180), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CWA: Local 1183, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - CWA: National Conventions, 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - CWA: Structure Review Committee Report, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Department of Buildings, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Department of Consumer Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Department of Corrections, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Department of Finance, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Department of Health, 1967-1972, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Department of Health: Performance Evaluation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Department of Highways, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Department of Hospitals, 1965-1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Department of Mental Health, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Department of Parks, 1963, 1971, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Department of Personnel, 1966-1974 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Department of Personnel, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Department of Probation, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Department of Social Services, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Department of Social Services, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Department of Social Services, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Department of Social Services, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Department of Social Services: Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Department of Social Services: Case Intake and Management, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Department of Social Services: Caseload Redistribution, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Department of Social Services: Directory, May 1974 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Department of Social Services: Division of Location and Support, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Department of Social Services: Face-to Face Recertification, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Department of Social Services: Field Auditors, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Department of Social Services: Office Managers, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Department of Social Services: Office of Community Services, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Department of Social Services: Salary Inequities, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Department of Social Services: Surplus Food Depots, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Department of Social Services: Theft of Checks, 1970, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Department of Social Services: Training, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Department of Social Services: Department of Traffic, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Direct Care Services, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Division of Field Audit, 1970, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dues, 1963-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Education, 1974, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Education Committee, 1974, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Education Fund, 1974, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1968, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Elections, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Elections: Stewards, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Control Board, 1961-1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Pay Policy, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Environmental Protection Administration, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Environmental Protection Administration, 1967-1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Exams, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board: Miscellaneous, 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Family Assistance Act, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Finance Administration, 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Finances, 1972-1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Fire Department, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Food Stamp Program, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Grievance Committee, 1977, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Grievance Representative: Applications, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation: Personnel Review Board, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation: Personnel Review Board, 1974, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation: Taylor Law Penalty Appeals, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Health and Hospital Corporation: Layoffs/Strike Proposals, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Health Services Administration, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Home Attendant Services, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Housing Authority, 1966-1977 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Housing and Development Administration, 1969-1975 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Housing and Development Administration, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Human Resources Administration, 1964-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Human Resources Administration, Jan 1973-Apr 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Human Resources Administration, May 1973-Jun 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Human Resources Administration, Jul 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Human Resources Administration, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Human Resources Administration, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)